In the mighty name of Jesus!
You, disease, wherever it is located in your organ -
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Disease in your organ, affliction in your organ, sickness in your organ -
begin to command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Tell them to come out!
Leave my people, you sickness!
A woman is vomiting poison and an object.
Please, camera department, move around to see the woman vomiting poison.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood, Poisonous Substances And Object
You poison!
[Out!]
Tell your neighbour, "Put your demand by faith on this!".
Out!
Vomiting Blood, Poisonous Substances And Object
I command you, in the name of Jesus!
This is Jesus.
Do you see blood coming out? Yes.
Vomiting Blood, Poisonous Substances And Object
There is a wonderful name, Jesus
There is no other name I know
The same name you can begin to call now with all your heart.
Mean it.
When you are calling the name, mean it.
There is a wonderful name, Jesus
There is no other name I know
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Millicent Kumah. I'm from Ghana.
Since about 15 years, I always ate in my dreams and whenever I woke up, I felt body pains,
especially in my waist, back and legs.
I felt pain all over my body.
I went to the hospital where I was given pain killers.
I took them, but still, I felt the pains all over my body.
So, one day I complained to a friend when I realised that this wasn't real
because the pain was too much, and despite taking pain killers, it was still the same. .
I said to myself that this was not just a sickness.
I told a friend of mine about my problem and she said, "Oh, my dear. Watch Emmanuel TV".
I said, "Ah, Emmanuel TV. What is that?"
She said, "Just watch and see".
From then, I began watching Emmanuel TV.
And I realised, "Ah! I wish I had known about it long before that".
I began watching it day and night. I always have Emmanuel TV on.
Whenever Prophet T.B. Joshua is praying, I always pray along with him.
I then decided to come to The SCOAN.
I came to The SCOAN last week.
When the man of God was praying during the mass prayer on Sunday,
"Wherever the sickness is located, be cast out! Be removed!",
I prayed along with him and put my hand where there was the pain, as he instructed.
I put my hand on my stomach and on my forehead.
All of a sudden, I felt an object in my mouth.
When I spat it out, blood started flowing out of my mouth.
When I saw the blood, I was surprised where this blood came from.
Then, I heard the man of God saying that I was given an object in the dream, which was the one coming out.
So, immediately the man of God started offering the mass prayer, you felt something coming out of you
which you vomited - that poisonous substance, just as the man of God had prophesied during the mass prayer
that there was somebody in the midst of the congregation vomiting poison.
Immediately, you were located right in the midst of the congregation,
as we are watching on the screen of our television, you were vomiting
that thick blood and poisonous substance as prophesied by the man of God.
Tell us what you felt in your system immediately you vomited that poisonous substance.
Immediately, the pain in my stomach, back, and my whole body (left).
I feel relieved. There is no more pain now.
The following day, I woke up feeling fresh, free, light.
No more pain. I thank God.
Thank You, Jesus, for healing me.
Put your hands together for Jesus Christ.
Can you tell us some of the things you were not able to do
as a result of this agonising pain you suffered from all over your body for 15 years.
Because of the pain, I could not walk for a long distance; when I walked a little, I felt tired.
I had to rest.
Can you tell us, madam: What efforts did you put in place
or where did you go to in search for solution to get rid of this problem in these 15 years?
During that time, I went to the hospital and I was first told
that I had to undergo an operation to remove the moving object.
I refused.
But the pain continued so I went back to the hospital.
I was told the same thing that I should undergo the operation but I still refused.
I didn't want to undergo an operation.
But now, I can bend down, no pain.
I can bend sideways. No pain.
There is no more pain at my back or in my breasts.
Thank You, Jesus, for healing me.
I am free, thank You, Jesus.
I am delivered, my family is delivered.
Thank You, Jesus. I am free.
Once again, put your hands together for the miracle working God.
What is your advice to people listening to you all over the world concerning what God has done in your life?
My advice is that you should depend on God.
We have a God, the Creator of all things and the Fountain of all perfection.
Thank You, Jesus. I am free.
We give glory to God Almighty and we want to advise you, sister, that God Almighty has set you free
and rescued you from a terrible situation of many years.
We advise you to trust in the Lord. continue to follow Him along the way,
make His Word the standard for your life and better is not good enough, we know the best is yet to come.
Can you just exercise yourself before you finally go?
Bend your waist and tell us how you are feeling.
Any more pains?
No more pain. I feel free.
Thank You, Jesus.
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for Jesus!